In this clip, we are going to go ahead and start putting in all of our dinosaur themed items.
I went down to my favorite discount store and I found a bunch of dinosaur things.
I totally lucked out.
I was very excited about it.
A dinosaur coloring book.
I loved getting these when I was little on Easter.
And this one even comes with its own crayons.
It?s very cute.
So I am going to put that there.
And then, in keeping with the spirit of Easter, I like to give Bibles, children's Bibles when I am creating Easter baskets for kids.
This is a very easy read and it is a picture Bible so little kids will have patience sitting through it.
And then, this is just a little coloring, a little poster coloring set with markers and dinosaur as you can see.
Put that there.
And a 3-D poster with some 3-D glasses.
And I think I am going to put that right there.
And these little guys.
These are little plastic dinosaur.
Boys love these.
And, there are going to go right there.
And then to round it off, some dinosaur stickers.
And these are actually hologram stickers.
I don't know if you can see but they are really kind of, they are cool, they are very cool.
So, i am going to put those right there. And there we have our dinosaur themed books and little paraphernalia And when we come back, I am going to show you how to embellish it even more with some more treats.